[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sangria is consumed all year round in this country. It is made of wine mixed with fruit and spices.", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Malta", "Ecuador", "Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Socrates, people should worry most about which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Their souls", "incorrect_answers": ["Their future", "Nothing at all", "Their health"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Lennon dropped out of high school.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Perfect Storm, what is the name of Bobbys girlfriend played by actress Diane Lane?", "correct_answer": "Christina", "incorrect_answers": ["Carol", "Cara", "Karen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Hundred Years War -- a series of related conflicts between France and England, started in 1337 and lasted how many years?", "correct_answer": "116", "incorrect_answers": ["100", "115", "117"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the total number of books in the New Testament of the Holy Bible.", "correct_answer": "27", "incorrect_answers": ["57", "37", "17"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Saw III, the classroom trap, the first trap we see, involves which character?", "correct_answer": "Troy", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeff", "Amanda", "Kerry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Navagio Bay (also known as the Shipwreck) is the most popular beach of which Greek island?", "correct_answer": "Zakynthos", "incorrect_answers": ["Mykonos", "Lefkada", "Thasos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you call the transfer of pollen grains from the anther to the stigma of flowers?", "correct_answer": "Pollination", "incorrect_answers": ["Reproduction", "Fertilization", "Migration"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would be from the Eastern Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "86", "incorrect_answers": ["72", "45", "63"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Alices cat in Alice in Wonderland?", "correct_answer": "Dinah", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheshire", "Dapple-Kit", "Rumpleteaser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the animated movie Cars, Guido provided the voice of Guido.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]